Guide to the Communications Workers of America, District 1 Records WAG.117
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America, District 1 Records
1946-2025, ongoing
1968-1982
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America. District 1
Allen, Clara
WAG.117
16 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
9 websites in 9 archived websites.
District 1 of the Communications Workers of America includes New York State, New Jersey, New England and parts of Eastern Canada. In its early years the District was comprised mainly of telephone workers, but its membership has diversified to include public employees (both state and local), journalists, healthcare workers, television and radio technicians and others. The collection contains correspondence, bargaining files, contracts, grievance files and general files.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Clara Allen on behalf of the Communications Workers of America, District 1, in 1994. The accession number associated with this gift is 1994.021.
http://district1.cwa-union.org/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2007 as part of the Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.) Web Archive. In 2015, this website was migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2020, https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1IH2MkKN8wtfguIRbeqbomNqVaw2jgws-/ and https://www.facebook.com/CWADistrict1/videos/3062527267112623/ were added to capture embedded photos and videos on the CWA District 1 website. The accession number associated with these websites are 2020.035. In March 2021, https://cwad1.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2021.078. In November 2021, https://www.safestaffingbuffalo.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2022.030. In March 2022, https://www.cwanj.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2022.053. In August 2022, https://kaleidaworkersunited.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2022.073. In September 2022, https://www.savenycallcenterjobs.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2022.077. In January 2023, https://cwasafestaffing.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2023.008. In May 2023, https://www.birdunion.org/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2023.044. In Spring 2025, https://audubon-union.glitch.me/ was added. The accession number associated with this website is 2025.063.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
District 1 of the Communications Workers of America is comprised of New York, New Jersey, New England. In its early years, immediately after the founding and consolidation of the CWA (1947-1951), the District was made up primarily of telephone workers. It was the nerve center and power base of the national union, whose early leaders and first president, Joseph Beirne, had come from the New York Metropolitan Area. Under District Director Mary Hanscomb the District gained steadily in size, but the biggest leap in numbers and political clout came when District organizer Morton Bahr (formerly president of Local 1172) and several associates succeeded in bringing in 24,000 workers of the New York Telephone Company (later NYNEX and still later part of Verizon). As a result of this campaign the membership of the District more than doubled. The two biggest locals in District 1, Local 1101 (New York Tel) and Local 1150 (AT&T Long-Lines) carried considerable weight in the affairs of the union nationally. Bahr served as New York State Director from 1961 to 1963, and assistant to District 1 Director George Miller from 1963 to 1969. During the 1960s Bahr and Miller fought off several attempts by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters to raid CWA locals, and oversaw the beginnings of what was to be a crucial area of expansion for CWA, the organizing of public workers.
Morton Bahr succeeded Miller in 1969 and assumed the new title of Vice-President for District 1. As the organizing gains of the 1960s were carried forward, tensions within the bargaining process began to make themselves felt throughout the telephone sector of the union.
In the summer of 1971 the CWA launched a strike against New York Telephone, which left lingering bitter feelings between the union and the Company. In addition, key elements in the District held out stubbornly in a "wild-cat" protest against President Beirne's initial attempts to reach a settlement in the strike, and the conflict stretched to 218 days. The settlement of the strike paved the way for national bargaining in telephone -- a long-held goal of the CWA -- finally achieved in 1974.
The present headquarters of the District, at 80 Pine St. in lower Manhattan was established in 1972. Vice-President Bahr served on the union's Bell System Bargaining Committee, and led the District's highly effective lobbying efforts in New York, New Jersey and Connecticut. He has said that the CWA was the most politically influential union the New York State during the 1980s.
In 1983 the huge International Operating Center in Manhattan was closed, resulting in a major lay-off of traffic workers. This was only one effect of the court-ordered AT&T divestiture, which took full effect in 1984, and resulted in major company restructuring and changes in working conditions.
Jan Pierce, formerly CWA Area Director for Upstate New York, served as assistant to Morton Bahr, and succeeded to the position of District Vice-President, when Bahr became national president of CWA in 1985. Pierce, known for his militant approach to labor issues, presided over the aftermath of divestiture at AT&T and beginnings of the sweeping change in the telephone industry, change that was to bring drastic downsizing and the transfer of much of the industry away from the urban centers of the Northeast. Larry Mancino took over as Vice-President of District 1, then numbering some 120,000 in its ranks, in 1996. Under Mancino the make-up of district membership continued to diversify, and increased through the merger of the CWA and several smaller unions. The district came to include nurses, librarians, clerical workers, television and radio technicians, and journalists in the private sector, as well as tens of thousands of state and local public workers.
Scope and Content Note
Series I, General Files, includes correspondence, grievance files and reports documenting daily business of union locals and their relations with the district and the international union. Notable are files of articles, correspondence, memos and other materials documenting the AT&T divestiture.
Series II, Bargaining Files, contains notes and documents describing negotiations of District 1 locals with AT & T, Bell Labs, ITT World Com, New Jersey Bell, Western Electric and Western Union, among many other employers. Also included are publicity materials and flyers urging member participation in strikes and demonstrations.
Series III, Archived Website, is made up of the archived websites for District 1, dating back to 2007. This series contains websites created by District 1 of the Communications Workers of America and its locals.
Arrangement
Organized into 3 series:
Series I, General Files
Series II, Bargaining Files
Series III, Archived Websites
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers or American Oral History Collection. (OH 26)
Records of the Communications Workers of America. (WAG 124)
Records of Communications Workers of America, Local 1150. (WAG 59)
Records of Communications Workers of America, Local 1180. (WAG 63)
Separated Material
Photographs from the collection were separated to the Non-Print Department of the Tamiment Library.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Labor leaders -- New York (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.).; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Government employee unions -- New York (State) -- New York; New Jersey.; New England; Collective bargaining -- New York (State); Reports.; Correspondence.; Contracts; Government employee unions -- New Jersey; Grievance procedures -- United States; Collective bargaining -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Telecommunication.; Corporate divestiture -- United States.; Strikes and lockouts -- Telephone companies -- New York (State) -- New York.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Telephone companies -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York.; Telephone operators -- New York (State) -- New York; Call centers; Nurses -- Labor unions -- United States.; Nonprofit organizations -- Employees -- United States; Bahr, Morton; Pierce, Jan.; Bell Telephone Laboratories; Bell Telephone Company; ITT World Communications Inc.; Communications Workers of America; New York Telephone Company; New Jersey Bell; Western Union Telegraph Company; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Long Lines Department; Western Electric Company; Allen, Clara; Communications Workers of America. District 1
- Series I: General Files, 1946-1987
  - Air India - Pay Adjustment, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AT&T Long Lines - Reclassification of Titles, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AT&T Long Lines - Tours Selection, 1946-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AT&T Long Lines - Wages, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Casino Gambling Panel, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: AT&T Long Lines-National Director, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: AT&T Long Lines-National Director, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: General I, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: General II, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: General, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: General, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: NYTel Plant Locals, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals III, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals I, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: NY Tel Plant Locals II, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Divestiture I, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Divestiture II, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Grievance: Local 1150 (Case #7P4-38) Promotion to Engineering Associates I, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grievance: Local 1150 (Case #7P4-38) Promotion to Engineering Associates II, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Havas et al. vs. CWA I, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Havas et al. vs. CWA II, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hot Line (District 1, newsletter), 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Job Value Analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local 1103: Appeal (Holden & Wooley), 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Local 1104: Election Appeal, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local 1120: NLRB Case, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NY Tel: Brotherhood of Telephone Workers, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NY Tel: Building and Garage Mechanics, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NY Tel: Contract Labor Dispute, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NY Tel: Employment Study, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NY Tel: Escorts (Arbitration Awards), 1968-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NY Tel: Exposure to Lead, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NY Tel: Habel Case, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NY Tel: Havas et al. vs. CWA, 1972-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NY Tel: High Crime Area Dispute (Arbitration Award), 1962-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NY Tel: High Crime Area Dispute (Bargaining), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NY Tel: High Crime Area Dispute (General), 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NY Tel: High Crime Area Dispute (Suspensions), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NY Tel: Import Program (Disputes), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NY Tel: Local 1101, By-laws and Election Disputes, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NY Tel: Local 1101, Defense Fund Settlement, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NY Tel: Local 1101, Dissident Literature and Dempsey Election, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NY Tel: Local 1101, Serrette, Dennis, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NY Tel: Local 1109 Election, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NY Tel: Loos vs. NY Tel, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NY Tel: Loos vs. NY Tel, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NY Tel: 1971 Strike, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NY Tel: 1971 Strike, Unemployment Compensation, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NY Tel: One Thousand Club, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NY Tel: Organizing, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NY Tel: Organizing, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NY Tel: Organizing, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NY Tel: Teamster Raid, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NY Tel: Technical Electronics and Communications Union (TECU), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NY Tel: Technical Electronics and Communications Union (TECU), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NY Tel: Technical Electronics and Communications Union (TECU), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NY Tel: Technical Electronics and Communications Union (TECU), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - NY Tel: Transfers, 1965, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - NY Tel: Wage Rates, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - OPEIU: Local 153 -- Agreements, 1964-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Parking Enforcement Agents (Assault Cases), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public Employees' Demands, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Roberts, F.D.: Grievance Case, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rockland County: NY Tel or Outside Tel System?, 1971-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Strikers' Unemployment Benefits (Supreme Court Case), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Suffolk County: Interconnect or NY Tel?, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - United Telephone Organization (UTO), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - White Plains Promotions, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Series II: Bargaining Files, 1966-1989
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining I, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining II, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining I, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining II, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - AT&T-Long Lines: Bargaining, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bell Labs: Bargaining, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Bell Labs: Bargaining, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Bell Labs: Bargaining, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Student Loan Foundation: Bargaining, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gloucester Board of Freeholders: Bargaining, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ITT World Com: Bargaining I, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ITT World Com: Bargaining II, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ITT World Com: Bargaining, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Interconnect Contractors Corp.: Bargaining, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local 1021 (Burlington Co., NJ, Board of Elections), undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 1036 (Township of Lacey, NJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local 1040 (Borough of Princeton, NJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local 1040 (Housing Authority of City of Trenton - Administrative), undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Local 1040 (Housing Authority of City of Trenton - Maintenance), undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Local 1040 (Housing Authority of City of Trenton - Supervisory), undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Local 1040 (Mercer County, NJ, Superintendent of Elections), undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Local 1040 (Montgomery, NJ, Blue Collar Workers Association), undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Local 1040 (Township of West Windsor, NJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local 1042 (Township of Hamilton, NJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Local 1043 (Ocean Co., NJ, Non-Supervisory White Collar Workers), undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Local 1064 (Monmouth Co., NJ, Youth Detention Center), undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Local 1065 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Roosevelt Hospital, Non-Professional Employees), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Local 1066 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Roosevelt Hospital) I, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Local 1066 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Roosevelt Hospital) II, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Local 1066 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Roosevelt Hospital) III, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Local 1066 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Roosevelt Hospital) IV, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Local 1067 (Board of Education, Cherry Hill, NJ), undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Local 1067 (Burlington, NJ, Day Care Center), undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Local 1067 (Camden, NJ, Regional Legal Services), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Local 1068 (Chatham, NJ, Joint Free Library), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 1068 (Maplewood, NJ, Memorial Library), undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 1068 (Nutley, NJ, Library), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Local 1069 (Morris Co., NJ, Board of Social Services) I, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Local 1069 (Morris Co., NJ, Board of Social Services) II, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Local 1070 (Long Beach, NJ, Township Blue Collar Group), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 1070 (Ocean Co., NJ, Blue Collar), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 1070 (Ocean Co., NJ, Board of Chosen Freeholders) I, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 1070 (Ocean Co., NJ, Board of Chosen Freeholders) II, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Local 1070 (Ocean Co., NJ, Mosquito Commission), undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Local 1070 (Ocean Co., NJ, Non-Supervisory Social Workers), undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Local 1070 (Stafford, NJ, Township Blue Collar Unit), undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Local 1071 (Warren Co., NJ, Board of Health), undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Local 1071 (Warren Co., NJ, Welfare Board - Non-Supervisory Employees), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Local 1071 (Warren Co., NJ, Welfare Board - Supervisory Employees), undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Local 1072 (Cablentertainment, NJ), undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Local 1072 (Group with Cable Inc., Wildwood, NJ), undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Local 1072 (South Jersey, Teleprompter Corp. - South Jersey TV Co.), undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Local 1072 (South Jersey, Teleprompter Corp. - South Jersey Television Cable Co.), undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Local 1074 (Paramus, NJ, Bergen Pines County Hospital) I, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Local 1074 (Paramus, NJ, Bergen Pines County Hospital) II, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Local 1075 (NJ, Telephone Company), undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Local 1076 (Millburn, NJ, Board of Education) I, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Local 1076 Millburn, NJ, Board of Education) II, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Local 1077 (Board of Water Commissioners, East Orange, NJ), undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Local 1077 (City of East Orange, NJ), undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Local 1079 (Camden, NJ, Board of Education), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Local 1081 (Essex Co., NJ, Welfare Board), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Local 1082 (Court Clerks, Middlesex Co., NJ) I, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Local 1082 (Court Clerks, Middlesex Co., NJ) II, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 1082 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Hospital for Chronically Ill) I, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 1082 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Hospital for Chronically Ill) II, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 1082 (Middlesex Co., NJ, Welfare Board), undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local 1082 (Township of North Brunswick, NJ), undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 1083 (Sussex Co. Welfare Board), 1973-1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Local 1084 (Camden Co., NJ, Welfare Board), 1973-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Local 1084 (Camden Co., NJ, Welfare Board), 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Local 1085 (Gloucester Co., NJ, Welfare Board), undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Local 1085 (Burlington Co., NJ, Welfare Board), undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Local 1087 (Monmouth Co., NJ, Board of Social Services), undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Local 1088 (Borough of Beachwood, NJ), undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Local 1089 (Bergen Co., NJ, Board of Social Services) I, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Local 1089 (Bergen Co., NJ, Board of Social Services) II, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Local 1109 (AIM Telephones, Fairfield, NJ), undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Local 1109 (Alpha Teleconnect Inc., Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 9, Folder 19)